(Penny:)Well, I might not have
asked you to dance then,
(Penny:)but I will ask you now.
There's no music.
(Howard:)I don't care.
(Penny:)We'll make
our own music.
(Leonard:)My God, who's the dork now?
(scoffs)
(giggles)
(Leonard:)Thank you for
wearing your flats.
wearing your heels.
Mmm.
(Leonard:)Look at me.
(Leonard:)Dancing with the prettiest
girl at the prom.
(Penny:)Want to take a picture
of us and send it
(Penny:)to your old friends
in the chess club?
(Leonard:)I sent them a bikini shot
of you years ago.
(Leonard:)This is nice.
(Leonard:)I kind of wish
no one else was coming.
(Penny:)I know, me, too.
(Penny:)But it will be fun to have a
prom without all the drama.
Howie, get off of him!